A lot of books are coming out right now from centrist politicians like Joe Manchin, Kamala
Harris, and Joe Biden. And when you look at the book covers, you're like, who in the fuck
would ever read this shit? It's about centrism, compromise, and losing to Trump's agenda.
These are people that fed us into the open mouth of hell. They have no wisdom to offer.
They have left us in ruins. Why would anybody read 300 pages that they probably didn't even
write? Their ghostwriter did it. And the reason is, it's a cynical money grab. This is the
way that politicians wash their money. How do these things rocket to number one on the charts,
the same place like where the Bible is or where the crawdads sing? It's because the people that
they did the dirty work for during their administrations, oil companies, banks, weapons
manufacturers, buy them in bulk, either through shell companies or subsidiaries, so that they
can artificially inflate the numbers. So this is just another way that politics is such
a grift. Because even if you lose, you win. Because you can write a book about how you valiantly
fought and lost to fascism. When in reality, you helped its ascendance. So congratulations on
your fucking book, Kamala Harris, Joe Manchin. I hope you're shouted down at every single stop
on your tour. I hope people never, ever leave you alone. Let's face it, Joe Biden's a little too old
to be out there, you know, talking. But yeah, may you never know a moment's peace because
these books are just cynical money grabs.